internationalhighlife.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy | International Highlife

## Terms Of Use

Highlife Media Consulting LLC (A registered legal entity in Switzerland) provides this Website and Services (located at [www.](http://www.internationalhighlife.com/)[internationalhighlife](http://www.internationalhighlife.com/)[.com](http://www.internationalhighlife.com/)) to you subject to the notices, terms, and conditions set forth in these terms (the “Terms of Use”). In addition, when you use any of our Services, you will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they are incorporated into this Terms of Use by this reference.

These Terms of Use are effective as of May 31, 2018.

## Privacy Policy

###  Tools and Plugin we use on www.internationalhighlife.com

  * Mailchimp – Newsletter
  * Google Analytics
  * Contact Form
  * Apache, NGINX Webserver
  * Adbutler Adserver
  * Affiliate Networks (Amzaon , RevContent, RevOffer, Amazon)
  * Social Media Plugins (Youtube, Facebook)
  * CleanTalk Anti-Spam & Security Plugin

### If you use this website you agree to the following conditions:

  * You are at least 18 years of age
  * You use the Website and Services according to these Terms of Use and all applicable laws and regulations determined by the state and country of residence
  * You provide complete and accurate registration information and maintain accurate registration information on the Website
  * You agree and understand that International Highlife may, at any time, and without prior notice, revoke and/or cancel your access if you fail to meet these criteria or violate any portion of these Terms of Use

Personal data (usually referred to just as “data” below) will only be processed by us to the extent necessary and for the purpose of providing a functional and user-friendly website, including its contents, and the services offered there.

Per Art. 4 No. 1 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, i.e. the General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the “GDPR”), “processing” refers to any operation or set of operations such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation, alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination, or otherwise making available, alignment, or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction performed on personal data, whether by automated means or not.

The following privacy policy is intended to inform you in particular about the type, scope, purpose, duration, and legal basis for the processing of such data either under our own control or in conjunction with others. We also inform you below about the third-party components we use to optimize our website and improve the user experience which may result in said third parties also processing data they collect and control.

Our privacy policy is structured as follows:

  1. Information about us as controllers of your data  
II. The rights of users and data subjects  
III. Information about the data processing

### I. Information about us as controllers of your data

The party responsible for this website (the “controller”) for purposes of data protection law is:

Highlife Media Consulting LLC  
Marco Cadisch  
Im Gässli 36  
8162 Steinmaur  
Switzerland  
www.highlife-media.com

Email: admin@highlife-media.com

### II. The rights of users and data subjects

With regard to the data processing to be described in more detail below, users and data subjects have the right

  * to confirm whether data concerning them is being processed, information about the data being processed, further information about the nature of the data processing, and copies of the data (cf. also Art. 15 GDPR);
  * to correct or complete incorrect or incomplete data (cf. also Art. 16 GDPR);
  * to the immediate deletion of data concerning them (cf. also Art. 17 DSGVO), or, alternatively, if further processing is necessary as stipulated in Art. 17 Para. 3 GDPR, to restrict said processing per Art. 18 GDPR;
  * to receive copies of the data concerning them and/or provided by them and to have the same transmitted to other providers/controllers (cf. also Art. 20 GDPR);
  * to file complaints with the supervisory authority if they believe that data concerning them is being processed by the controller in breach of data protection provisions (see also Art. 77 GDPR).

In addition, the controller is obliged to inform all recipients to whom it discloses data of any such corrections, deletions, or restrictions placed on processing the same per Art. 16, 17 Para. 1, 18 GDPR. However, this obligation does not apply if such notification is impossible or involves a disproportionate effort. Nevertheless, users have a right to information about these recipients.

Likewise, under Art. 21 GDPR, users and data subjects have the right to object to the controller’s future processing of their data pursuant to Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. In particular, an objection to data processing for the purpose of direct advertising is permissible.

### III. Information about the data processing

Your data processed when using our website will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for its storage ceases to apply, provided the deletion of the same is not in breach of any statutory storage obligations or unless otherwise stipulated below.

#### Server data

For technical reasons, the following data sent by your internet browser to us or to our server provider will be collected, especially to ensure a secure and stable website: These server log files record the type and version of your browser, operating system, the website from which you came (referrer URL), the webpages on our site visited, the date and time of your visit, as well as the IP address from which you visited our site.

The data thus collected will be temporarily stored, but not in association with any other of your data.

The basis for this storage is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the improvement, stability, functionality, and security of our website.

The data will be deleted within no more than seven days, unless continued storage is required for evidentiary purposes. In which case, all or part of the data will be excluded from deletion until the investigation of the relevant incident is finally resolved.

#### Cookies

##### a) Session cookies

We use cookies on our website. Cookies are small text files or other storage technologies stored on your computer by your browser. These cookies process certain specific information about you, such as your browser, location data, or IP address.

This processing makes our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure, allowing us, for example, to display our website in different languages or to offer a shopping cart function.

The legal basis for such processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR, insofar as these cookies are used to collect data to initiate or process contractual relationships.

If the processing does not serve to initiate or process a contract, our legitimate interest lies in improving the functionality of our website. The legal basis is then Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR.

When you close your browser, these session cookies are deleted.

##### b) Third-party cookies

If necessary, our website may also use cookies from companies with whom we cooperate for the purpose of advertising, analyzing, or improving the features of our website.

Please refer to the following information for details, in particular for the legal basis and purpose of such third-party collection and processing of data collected through cookies.

##### c) Disabling cookies

You can refuse the use of cookies by changing the settings on your browser. Likewise, you can use the browser to delete cookies that have already been stored. However, the steps and measures required vary, depending on the browser you use. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your browser or contact its maker for support. Browser settings cannot prevent so-called flash cookies from being set. Instead, you will need to change the setting of your Flash player. The steps and measures required for this also depend on the Flash player you are using. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your Flash player or contact its maker for support.

If you prevent or restrict the installation of cookies, not all of the functions on our site may be fully usable.

#### Newsletter

If you register for our free newsletter, the data requested from you for this purpose, i.e. your email address and, optionally, your name and address, will be sent to us. We also store the IP address of your computer and the date and time of your registration. During the registration process, we will obtain your consent to receive this newsletter and the type of content it will offer, with reference made to this privacy policy. The data collected will be used exclusively to send the newsletter and will not be passed on to third parties.

The legal basis for this is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR.

You may revoke your prior consent to receive this newsletter under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent or click on the unsubscribe link contained in each newsletter.

#### Contact

If you contact us via email or the contact form, the data you provide will be used for the purpose of processing your request. We must have this data in order to process and answer your inquiry; otherwise we will not be able to answer it in full or at all.

The legal basis for this data processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.

Your data will be deleted once we have fully answered your inquiry and there is no further legal obligation to store your data, such as if an order or contract resulted therefrom.

#### User posts, comments, and ratings

We offer you the opportunity to post questions, answers, opinions, and ratings on our website, hereinafter referred to jointly as “posts.” If you make use of this opportunity, we will process and publish your post, the date and time you submitted it, and any pseudonym you may have used.

The legal basis for this is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR. You may revoke your prior consent under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent.

In addition, we will also process your IP address and email address. The IP address is processed because we might have a legitimate interest in taking or supporting further action if your post infringes the rights of third parties and/or is otherwise unlawful.

In this case, the legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in any legal defense we may have to mount

#### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics on our website. This is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google guarantees that it will follow the EU’s data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The Google Analytics service is used to analyze how our website is used. The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the analysis, optimization, and economic operation of our site.

Usage and user-related information, such as IP address, place, time, or frequency of your visits to our website will be transmitted to a Google server in the United States and stored there. However, we use Google Analytics with the so-called anonymization function, whereby Google truncates the IP address within the EU or the EEA before it is transmitted to the US.

The data collected in this way is in turn used by Google to provide us with an evaluation of visits to our website and what visitors do once there. This data can also be used to provide other services related to the use of our website and of the internet in general.

Google states that it will not connect your IP address to other data. In addition, Google provides further information with regard to its data protection practices at

including options you can exercise to prevent such use of your data.

In addition, Google offers an opt-out add-on at

in addition with further information. This add-on can be installed on the most popular browsers and offers you further control over the data that Google collects when you visit our website. The add-on informs Google Analytics’ JavaScript (ga.js) that no information about the website visit should be transmitted to Google Analytics. However, this does not prevent information from being transmitted to us or to other web analytics services we may use as detailed herein.

#### Adbutler tracking cookies

AdButler is the adserver-technology that we use to serve ads. AdButler only has two features that involve cookies to carry out their respective functionalities. Both of these cookies do not store any personal data (including personal IDs).

AdButler Frequency Capping Cookie

  * Data Collected: 
    * A non-personal ID that links to the zone and/or advertisement (not the individual)
    * A timestamp
  * Purpose of Cookie: 
    * Ensure that a user does not see the advertisement repeatedly
  * Duration of Data Stored: 
    * The duration for this cookie is set by the administrator within the AdButler interface each time it is used
  * Extent of Data Processing: 
    * The data this cookie collects is not shared with any third-parties and is used exclusively by AdButler for the reason mentioned above

AdButler Conversion Tracking Cookie

  * Data Collected: 
    * A non-personal ID that links to the zone and/or advertisement (not the individual)
  * Purpose of Cookie: 
    * Allow attribution of an advertisement to a desired goal. This does not track an individual, only the source advertisement
  * Duration of Data Stored: 
    * This cookie expires within 180 days
  * Extent of Data Processing: 
    * The data this cookie collects is not shared with any third-parties and is used exclusively by AdButler for the purpose mentioned
    * above

####  Facebook plug-in

Our website uses the plug-in of the Facebook social network. Facebook.com is a service provided by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. In the EU, this service is also operated by Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland, hereinafter both referred to as “Facebook.”

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active)

Facebook guarantees that it will follow the EU’s data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in improving the quality of our website.

Further information about the possible plug-ins and their respective functions is available from Facebook at

<https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>

If the plug-in is stored on one of the pages you visit on our website, your browser will download an icon for the plug-in from Facebook’s servers in the USA. For technical reasons, it is necessary for Facebook to process your IP address. In addition, the date and time of your visit to our website will also be recorded.

If you are logged in to Facebook while visiting one of our plugged-in websites, the information collected by the plug-in from your specific visit will be recognized by Facebook. The information collected may then be assigned to your personal account at Facebook. If, for example, you use the Facebook Like button, this information will be stored in your Facebook account and published on the Facebook platform. If you want to prevent this, you must either log out of Facebook before visiting our website or use an add-on for your browser to prevent the Facebook plug-in from loading.

Further information about the collection and use of data as well as your rights and protection options in Facebook’s privacy policy found at

<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

#### YouTube

We use YouTube on our website. This is a video portal operated by YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave, 94066 San Bruno, CA, USA, hereinafter referred to as “YouTube”.

YouTube is a subsidiary of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as “Google”.

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google and its subsidiary YouTube guarantee that they will follow the EU’s data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

We use YouTube in its advanced privacy mode to show you videos. The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in improving the quality of our website. According to YouTube, the advanced privacy mode means that the data specified below will only be transmitted to the YouTube server if you actually start a video.

Without this mode, a connection to the YouTube server in the USA will be established as soon as you access any of our webpages on which a YouTube video is embedded.

This connection is required in order to be able to display the respective video on our website within your browser. YouTube will record and process at a minimum your IP address, the date and time the video was displayed, as well as the website you visited. In addition, a connection to the DoubleClick advertising network of Google is established.

If you are logged in to YouTube when you access our site, YouTube will assign the connection information to your YouTube account. To prevent this, you must either log out of YouTube before visiting our site or make the appropriate settings in your YouTube account.

For the purpose of functionality and analysis of usage behavior, YouTube permanently stores cookies on your device via your browser. If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.

Further information about the collection and use of data as well as your rights and protection options in Google’s privacy policy found at

<https://policies.google.com/privacy>

#### MailChimp – Newsletter

We offer you the opportunity to register for our free newsletter via our website.

We use MailChimp, a service of The Rocket Science Group, LLC, 512 Means Street, Suite 404, Atlanta, GA 30318, USA, hereinafter referred to as “The Rocket Science Group”.

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG&status=Active)

the Rocket Science Group guarantees that it will follow the EU’s data protection regulations when processing data in the United States. In addition, the Rocket Science Group offers further information about its data protection practices at

<http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

If you register for our free newsletter, the data requested from you for this purpose, i.e. your email address and, optionally, your name and address, will be processed by The Rocket Science Group. In addition, your IP address and the date and time of your registration will be saved. During the registration process, your consent to receive this newsletter will be obtained together with a concrete description of the type of content it will offer and reference made to this privacy policy.

The newsletter then sent out by The Rocket Science Group will also contain a tracking pixel called a web beacon. This pixel helps us evaluate whether and when you have read our newsletter and whether you have clicked any links contained therein. In addition to further technical data, such as data about your computer hardware and your IP address, the data processed will be stored so that we can optimize our newsletter and respond to the wishes of our readers. The data will therefore increase the quality and attractiveness of our newsletter.

The legal basis for sending the newsletter and the analysis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR.

You may revoke your prior consent to receive this newsletter under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent or click on the unsubscribe link contained in each newsletter.

#### Affiliate tracking cookies

We also advertise third-party offers and services on our website. If you enter into a contract with the third party after viewing our advertising for these third party offers, we will receive a commission for this referral.

We use the affiliate tracking cookie to record this successful conversion. However, this cookie does not store any of your personal data. Only our identification number as the affiliate advertiser and the serial number of the advertising material you clicked on (e.g. a banner or a text link) are recorded. We need this information for the purpose of processing and/or receiving payment of our commissions.

If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.

#### CleanTalk Anti-Spam & Security log files 

CleanTalk uses Cookies to manage access to the website by the CleanTalk SpamFireWall Function, to secure and to protect this website from spam.

The moment a visitor sends POST request such as comment, registration or contact form submission, the CleanTalk Anti-Spam receives and processes the following personal data if they exist: IP address, e-mail, text and values of each filled form field. Therefore each website form should grant a visitor the ability to give permission to process and keep these data.

Personal Data Management

At any moment you can delete information of any request via your [CleanTalk Control Panel](https://cleantalk.org/my/show_requests).

You can choose how long the service should keep data: 7 or 45 days or do not keep approved requests at all. <https://cleantalk.org/my/profile>

You also can exclude any website form fields from sending their data to the CleanTalk Anti-Spam or you can set a list of website pages for CleanTalk to ignore them completely.
